{
    "id": "9f35fd189a14420ead4b0eb1870d6734",
    "title": "Wish",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I wish I ……………… speak English.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "87fab2cb07a540a7bc8a58faf1adeb20"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you ………………… stop making that noise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c79f4ebc72e451ab6bce14a22ec0444"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. to the manager.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wish to talk",
                "am wishing to talk",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fba2b7c3af9e444ea05bed58bd00dcb3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish that I ………………… better looking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "am"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fba6710de3204819ad96c1401a4bd683"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. your exams.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wish you would pass",
                "hope you pass"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7409d5f34bac444a8b115121a00ecabb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I …………………. there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "51c1a2d7b59749d4a1d42fad0f18434d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ………………… that yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hadn't said",
                "didn't say"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "35a7f3fdd56943ec887e2dac96d07f54"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you …………………. stop smoking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c4e61d428d3845839abafaad27db66ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish today ………………… Sunday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "would be"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bea5842352cb438da99f7bda0620e746"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ………………… somewhere else.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lived"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9552c6b31aae45deacd25445d2b39679"
        }
    ]
}